http://www.edmonton.ymca.ca/future/our-story-privacy

Edmonton
Castle Downs Family YMCA (North)
Don Wheaton Family YMCA (downtown)
Jamie Platz Family YMCA (West)
William Lutsky Family YMCA (South)
Edmonton Rates
Join Now!
Join Now!
Temporary restrictions on recreation, effective December 13
Effective December 13, our William Lutsky Family YMCA, Jamie Platz Family YMCA and Don Wheaton Family YMCA are closed until further notice. The Northside Community Centre in Red Deer, Boyle Street Community Centre and YMCA Family Resource Centre in Edmonton, along with the Eagle Ridge Community Centre in Wood Buffalo are closed until further notice. Please click here for more information on current programs and services.
Please note, the restrictions announced on December 13th do not impact YMCA Child Care or community and housing programs and services.
Breadcrumb
Home
PRIVACY & INFORMATION PROTECTION
PRIVACY & INFORMATION PROTECTION
PRIVACY & INFORMATION PROTECTION
YMCA of Northern Alberta is committed to protecting your right to privacy and protecting your personal information. We protect your personal information and adhere to all legislative requirements with respect to protecting privacy. The personal information you share with the YMCA will be used to support the work of YMCA of Northern Alberta and YMCA Foundation.
Learn more about by reviewing the YMCA’s Privacy and Information Protection Policy.
Why is personal information collected?
YMCA of Northern Alberta asks for personal information for a variety of purposes, which further the charitable work of the YMCA. These purposes include, but are not limited to:
Volunteer relations
Relationship development and fundraising
Safety and security
YMCA membership services
Program and service registration and development
Employment relations
Legal, regulatory and contractual requirements
Supporting participants needs and eligibility for other services in the community
Where to get more information?
If you have questions or concerns about the YMCA's privacy practices, please direct your questions in writing to, YMCA Privacy Officer, with your contact information, and we will be happy to respond.
Privacy Officer
YMCA of Northern Alberta
10211-105 Street
Edmonton, AB T5J 1E3
phone: (780) 429-5739
e-mail: communications@northernalberta.ymca.ca
Our Programs
Aquatics
